{
    "subject": "resource/Emanuel_Calvo",
    "predicate": "ontology/birthPlace",
    "object": "resource/Thessaloniki",
    "human_readable": "Emanuel Calvo was born in Thessaloniki.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.8669834733009338,
            "question": "Name the city where Emanuel Calvo was born."
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8653895854949951,
            "question": "Where was Emanuel Calvo born?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7874599099159241,
            "question": "In what year was Emanuel Calvo born?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6972615122795105,
            "question": "What nationality is Emanuel Calvo?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4923401176929474,
            "question": "What is Emanuel Calvo known for?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4728392958641052,
            "question": "What country is Thessaloniki in?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.3400888442993164,
            "question": "Does Emanuel Calvo have any famous relatives?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.274143785238266,
            "question": "Are there any famous landmarks in Thessaloniki?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.21854731440544128,
            "question": "Is Thessaloniki a large city?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.19739073514938354,
            "question": "What is the climate like in Thessaloniki?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Emanuel Calvo was born in Thessaloniki.",
            "html": "dbpedia_8120_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Is Thessaloniki a large city?",
            "html": "dbpedia_8120_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Are there any famous landmarks in Thessaloniki?",
            "html": "dbpedia_8120_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Does Emanuel Calvo have any famous relatives?",
            "html": "dbpedia_8120_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8120_11.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8120_18.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8120_21.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8120_26.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8120_3.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8120_32.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8120_36.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8120_37.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8120_42.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8120_7.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": "Here is the structured JSON format for the query:\n\n```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"no\"\n}\n```\n\nThe reasoning behind this answer is that there are multiple documents that mention Emmanuel/Emmanuel/Emanuel Calvo, but only one of them (file_path: /Users/stefanomarchesin/Research/fshami/Rag/docs/dbpedia_8120/re-ranker-msmarco/21.txt) mentions his birthplace as Thessaloniki. However, this document is from the 18th century and refers to a different person than the one mentioned in the other documents (file_path: /Users/stefanomarchesin/Research/fshami/Rag/docs/dbpedia_8120/re-ranker-msmarco/3.txt), who was born in 1990. Therefore, it is not clear which Emmanuel Calvo was born in Thessaloniki."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\nThe documents state that \"Emanuel Calvo (late-seventeenth century - before 1772) was an Italian physician and Neo-Hebraic poet; born at Thessaloniki.\" This supports the statement that Emanuel Calvo was born in Thessaloniki."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Extremely Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {
        "llama3.1": {
            "reason": "Emanuel Calvo (late-seventeenth century - before 1772) was mentioned to be born at Thessaloniki in information 3 and 6, but a different person named Emmanuel Calvo was mentioned to be born in Oakland, Calif. in information 2, which seems to refer to the same time period as Emanuel Calvo (late-seventeenth century - before 1772).",
            "category": 2
        }
    }
}